<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Holly Gregorio</title>
    <link>https://cloudwarp.org/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Holly Gregorio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cloudwarp.org/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Pineapple Defense</title>
      <link>https://cloudwarp.org/projects/pineapple-defense/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudwarp.org/projects/pineapple-defense/</guid>
      <description>Pineapple defense is a simple tower defense game where you must defend you master pineapple from waves of pizza monsters.
About Development Pineapple Defense was made in Unity as a part of a challenge to make a game that had the theme of pineapples. The game is based on the old flash game Desktop Tower Defense but changes things up with new enemy types, crazier towers, and a new strategy of placing your master pineapple and protecting it as waves come from all directions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mob Scarecrows Mod</title>
      <link>https://cloudwarp.org/projects/mob-scarecrows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudwarp.org/projects/mob-scarecrows/</guid>
      <description>This mod adds many cute plushies and scarecrows into minecraft which can be used to scare away mobs or attract them.
1,000,000 + Downloads
About The Mod The mod has many different scarecrows which look like plushies that are used to keep mobs away from your base. The scarecrows are entities that can be placed anywhere and different scarecrows scare different mobs. Some scarecrows attract mobs making them very useful for mob farms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doodads Mod</title>
      <link>https://cloudwarp.org/projects/doodads/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudwarp.org/projects/doodads/</guid>
      <description>This mod will add 250+ items, blocks, and accessories.
What To Expect Doodads is a mod that will add over 250 different items and accessories to minecraft. I will be releasing this mod in sections which could be anywhere from 1 - 20 items at a time. Everything will be very configurable.
All names, items, and uses are not final as many are based on terraria accessories. If you see it here that is no guarantee that it will make it into the mod.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Probably Chests Mod</title>
      <link>https://cloudwarp.org/projects/probably-chests/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudwarp.org/projects/probably-chests/</guid>
      <description>This mod adds pots and chests that spawn all over the world, but beware as some chests are more than meets the eye.
480,000 + Downloads
About The Mod The mod adds many different biome specific pots and chests that spawn all over the world which can contain amazing loot. You can smash the pots to get simple items you need for caving while the rare chests can contain a huge range of items.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Faster Tools Mod</title>
      <link>https://cloudwarp.org/projects/faster-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudwarp.org/projects/faster-tools/</guid>
      <description>This mod increases the default tool speed in minecraft by 25% and can be customized.
About The Mod The mod simply increases the default tool speed by 25%. The tool speed can be changed via the config where the default value is 1.25 which sets the current tool speed to 25% faster than default.
Check it out HERE.
Come talk about the mod on the discord.
GitHub</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
