<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Holly Gregorio</title>
    <link>https://cloudwarp.org/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Holly Gregorio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cloudwarp.org/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Doodads Mod</title>
      <link>https://cloudwarp.org/projects/doodads/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudwarp.org/projects/doodads/</guid>
      <description>This mod will add 250+ items, blocks, and accessories.
What To Expect Doodads is a mod that will add over 250 different items and accessories to minecraft. I will be releasing this mod in sections which could be anywhere from 1 - 20 items at a time. Everything will be very configurable.
All names, items, and uses are not final as many are based on terraria accessories. If you see it here that is no guarantee that it will make it into the mod.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Probably Chests Mod</title>
      <link>https://cloudwarp.org/projects/probably-chests/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudwarp.org/projects/probably-chests/</guid>
      <description>This mod adds pots and chests that spawn all over the world, but beware as some chests are more than meets the eye.
8,000 + Downloads
About Development Probably Chests is a minecraft mod made for the fabric loader. It is my third Minecraft mod; created in April of 2022. Creating this mod was a new challenge as I got to learn how to use the GeckoLib library to create interesting animations for the mimics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Faster Tools Mod</title>
      <link>https://cloudwarp.org/projects/faster-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudwarp.org/projects/faster-tools/</guid>
      <description>This mod increases the default tool speed in minecraft by 25% and can be customized.
About Development Faster Tools is a minecraft mod made for the fabric loader. It is my second Minecraft mod; created in February of 2022. After creating my Mob Scarecrows mod I wanted to make a mod that fixed something that had always bugged me in minecraft which was the incredibly slow tool speed. Making this mod was harder than it seemed because initially I had to inject into 4 different places in both minecrafts and fabric’s code to modify the resulting tool speed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mob Scarecrows Mod</title>
      <link>https://cloudwarp.org/projects/mob-scarecrows/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudwarp.org/projects/mob-scarecrows/</guid>
      <description>This mod adds many cute plushies and scarecrows into minecraft which can be used to scare away mobs or attract them.
500,000 + Downloads
About Development Mob scarecrows is a minecraft mod made for the fabric loader. It was my first Minecraft mod; created in January of 2022. I had never made a minecraft mod before and thought I would do something simple like making a scarecrow to keep mobs away.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
